https://www.mavenecommerce.com/privacy-policy

Introduction
We are committed to respecting your online privacy and we recognize your need for the protection and management of any Personal Information that you share with us. We provide this Privacy Policy to explain our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your Personal Information is collected and used in connection with the Site. “Personal Information” means any information that may be used, either alone or in combination with other information, to personally identify an individual, including, but not limited to, a first and last name, personal profile, a home or other physical address, an email address or other contact information.
Your Consent
By using the Site, you consent to the terms of our Privacy Policy and to our processing of Personal Information for the purposes stated herein. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, then please do not use the Site. We reserve the right, at our discretion, to change this Privacy Policy at any time. Such change will be effective ten (10) days following posting of the revised Privacy Policy on the Site and your continued use of the Site thereafter means that you accept those changes.
General Use of the Site
We do not currently require you to provide Personal Information in order to have access to general information available on the Site other than in order to post comments on the User Communication Platforms. Maven eCommerce reserves the right to change such matter from time to time, as set forth herein.
What Personal Information We Collect and How We Collect It
We receive and/or collect Personal Information from you in the following ways:
Account. In order to provide you with certain services that we may offer through the Site, we may request that you register an account (“Account”). For example, such an Account may be required in order to post a comment onto the User Communication Platforms. As part of the Account registration process, you will be asked to provide us certain mandatory Personal Information such as your username, first name, phone number, email address, company name, a password that you will use in connection with your Account, and other designated information. You may also choose to provide your fax number, date of birth, job title, website, country, a company contact person, and other information. We do not intend to make any of your Account information publicly available on the Site other than if you comment on the User Communication Platform, then we may display a partially obscured version of your user name on the Site as part of the User Communication Platform.
‘Contact Us’ or ‘Update’ request Information. If you send us a “contact us” request or “request to receive updates” we will receive and store a copy of your name, email address, telephone, and country, as well as any other Personal Information that you choose to disclose.
Log Files. The Site may make use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, clicked pages and any other information your browser may send to us. We may use such information to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the Site, and gather demographic information.
Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies. Some of our Site pages may utilize “cookies” and other tracking technologies. A “cookie” is a small text file that may be used, for example, to collect information about Site activity. Certain cookies and other technologies may serve to recall Personal Information, such as an IP address, previously indicated by a Site user. Most browsers allow you to control cookies, including whether or not to accept them and how to remove them. You may set most browsers to notify you if you receive a cookie, or you may choose to block cookies with your browser. If you block or delete “cookies” you may find the usefulness of our Site or parts of it to be impaired.
Use of Personal Information
If you submit Personal Information to us through the Site, Account User Submissions or any other way, then such Personal Information may be used in the following ways:
We will use your Personal Information to provide (and improve) the Site and our related services to you, to contact you in connection with the Site and its related services (including for the purpose of notifying you about our offers, products and/or services) and to identify and authenticate your access to the parts of the Site and the related services that you are authorized to access, such as the User Communication Platforms.
We may use your Personal Information to contact you in response to a “contact us” request or an “update” request.
We may provide Personal Information to our subsidiaries and affiliated companies for the purpose of processing or storing such information on our behalf. Such information may be transferred to other countries around the world. We require that these parties agree to process such information in compliance with our Privacy Policy.
We may share your Personal Information with our third party service providers (such as a hosting provider, service provider or a payment processor), but only to assist us with our business operations and to provide the Site and its related services. Such information may be transferred to other countries around the world. We use commercially reasonable efforts to only engage or interact with third-party service providers that post a Privacy Policy governing their processing of Personal Information.
We may disclose your Personal Information or any information you submit, if we have a good faith belief that disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary, to: (i) comply with any applicable law, regulation, legal process or governmental request, (ii) enforce our Terms including investigations of potential violations thereof, (iii) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud or security issues, and/or (iv) protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of Maven eCommerce, its users, yourself or the public.
Use of Anonymous Information
We may use Anonymous Information or disclose it to third party service providers in order to provide and improve our Site and to enhance your experience with it. We may also disclose Anonymous Information (with or without compensation) to third parties, including advertisers and partners, for purposes including, but not limited to, targeted advertisements. “Anonymous Information” means information which does not enable identification of an individual user, such as aggregated information about the use of our Site.
Opt-out
We may use your email address to send promotions, updates, a newsletter or news regarding our Site, service and products. You may choose not to receive future emails from us by pressing an unsubscribe link added at the bottom of each email that you receive from us or by sending a single email with the subject “BLOCK” to contacts@mavenecommerce.com. Please note that the email must come from the email account you wish to block. Please note that even if you opt out of receiving the foregoing emails, we may still send you a response to any “Contact Us” request as well as administrative emails (for example, in connection with a password reset request) that are necessary to facilitate your use of the Site or the Account. If you wish to delete or deactivate your Account you can contact us at contacts@mavenecommerce.com and include adequate details of your request. Your email must contain the following topic: “DEACTIVATION OF ACCOUNT”.
Changes to Your Personal Information
To the extent that you do provide us with Personal Information, please ensure that it remains accurate. If your Personal Information changes, or you wish to remove or modify certain Personal Information that we are storing, you may either correct or update it by logging-in to your Account and making the change(s), or by contacting us at contacts@mavenecommerce.com. Your email should include adequate details of your request and also contain the following email topic: “PERSONAL INFORMATION UPDATE REQUEST”. We will provide initial responses to such requests within a reasonable period of time.
Choice
At all times, you may choose whether or not to provide Personal Information to Maven eCommerce. The notices that we provide on the Site in circumstances where we collect Personal Information should help you make this choice. If you choose not to provide the Personal Information we request, you can still use the Site, but you may be unable to access certain options, offers, and services that involve our interaction with you.
Links to Other Sites
Our Site may contain links to other sites. Other sites may also reference or link to our Site. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such other sites.
Children’s Privacy
The Site is not intended for children under the age of 18 years old, and we do not intend to collect Personal Information from anyone we know to be under 18 years of age.
Security
The security of your Personal Information is important to us. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the Personal Information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, We cannot guarantee absolute security. If you have any questions about security on the Site, you can contact us contacts@mavenecommerce.com.
Merger, Sale or Bankruptcy
In the event that we are acquired by or merged with a third party entity, or in the event of bankruptcy or a comparable event, we reserve the right to transfer or assign Personal Information in connection with the foregoing event.
Commitment
We are committed to protecting your privacy. Protecting your privacy online is an evolving area, and we are constantly evolving our Site to meet these demands. If you have any comments or questions regarding our Privacy Policy, or your Personal Information that we may be storing and using, please contact us contacts@mavenecommerce.com.
